(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-20T02:09:47.144038",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Tokoyami Towa 6th Anniversary LIVE
常闇トワ 6周年記念 Rock Festa!!!
Tokoyami Towa 6th Anniversary Rock Festa!!!
Artist
常闇トワ
Tokoyami Towa
Guest
鷹嶺ルイ
Takane Lui
輪堂千速
Rindo Chihaya
IRyS
音乃瀬奏
Otonose Kanade
AZKi
夏色まつり
Natsuiro Matsuri
森カリオペ
Mori Calliope
猫汰つな
Nekota Tsuna
あぁ 呆れだす粗暴に差し替えられた
Ah, replaced by shocking rudeness,
現存に掛かった固定解答
an established answer applied to reality.
反則じみた応えじゃ見透かされてしまうな
With a response like cheating, I'll be seen through.
この道を渡りきっても まだ視界は曇っている
Even if I cross this road, my vision is still cloudy.
履き替えた大人になってから 縮みきった歩幅と感情
Since becoming an adult who changed shoes, my stride and emotions have shrunk.
削れだした身体に対して 「気付け」と唄ってる
I sing "Wake up!" to my worn-out body.
はみ出した情じゃ居られないのならさ
If I can't stay with my overflowing emotions,
染み付いたこの青さを切り離してしまっていい？
is it okay to cut away this deeply stained youth?
ずっと語りかいていた日々を嘆くように
As if lamenting the days I kept talking to...
「深い闇に飲み込まれないよう」って
..."So that I won't be swallowed by the deep darkness."
染まりきった現実に 答えなんてない
In a fully dyed reality, there is no answer.
逃げ出してしまった 言葉を羽織って
I ran away, cloaking myself in words.
溶けだした心を胸に隠している
I hide my melting heart in my chest,
冷え切ってしまった身体を騙すように
as if deceiving my completely chilled body.
描きかけた何時かの枯れた夢をなぞっている
I trace a withered dream from sometime in the past.
あぁ 暴れだす言葉に差し替えられた
Ah, replaced by rampaging words,
幻想に掛かった固定概念と
with an established stereotype applied to fantasy,
留まった理想じゃ見透かされてしまうな
and stagnant ideals, I will be seen through.
この道を渡りきっても また次回だ 続いていく
Even if I cross this road, it continues on to the next time.
履き違えた大人になってから 尖りだした思いの回想
Since becoming an adult with a misunderstanding, recalling my sharpening thoughts,
ずっと見えなくなった足跡探ししている
I've been searching for footprints that disappeared long ago.
はみ出した心じゃ居られないのならさ
If I can't stay with my overflowing heart,
澄み切ったこの青さを曝け出してしまっていい？
is it okay to expose this clear youth?
ずっと語りかいていたヒビを隠すように
As if hiding the cracks I kept talking to...
「深い闇に飲み込まれないよう」って
..."So that I won't be swallowed by the deep darkness."
決まりきった現実に 答えなんていらない
In a predetermined reality, I don't need any answers.
逃げ出してしまった 言葉を羽織って
I ran away, cloaking myself in words.
溶けだした心を胸に隠している
I hide my melting heart in my chest,
冷え切ってしまった身体を騙すように
as if deceiving my completely chilled body.
描きかけた何時かの枯れた夢をなぞって
I trace a withered dream from sometime in the past.
あぁ 錆び付いてる今をただ不安定に立つ
Ah, standing unstably in a rusted present.
裏返る脳裏に汚されてしまったあの日達
Those days polluted inside my inverted mind...
願っては辿ってた手放してしまったのに
Even though I wished and followed, even though I let go...
のに
...even so.
逃げ出してしまった 言葉を羽織って
I ran away, cloaking myself in words.
溶けだした心を胸に隠している
I hide my melting heart in my chest,
冷え切ってしまった身体を騙すように
as if deceiving my completely chilled body.
描きかけた何時かの枯れた夢をなぞっている
I trace a withered dream from sometime in the past.
Can you hear me when I cry in desperation?
Nothing comes along with my expectation
How much pain and ache you're feeling?
Breathing?
I gotta change this situation
アダルトスーツ
[Song: Adult Suit]
アダルトなキグルミ着てる僕
Wears an adult mascot costume...
心はいつも不安定 天秤シーソー
my heart is always unstable, like a seesaw.
まさかの発言で凍り付かす
Freezing people with unexpected remarks...
色目見え隠れ 血迷うボク
hiding my true colors, getting lost.
今日の今この瞬間に放とうとする
The words I try to let out...
言葉がいつも後ろ髪引く
in this very moment always pull me back.
全部ダメダメなんでしょ？じゃあもう放棄して！
Everything is no good, right? Then just abandon it!
ハナから無かった事にしよう固い
Let's pretend it never happened from the start!
ラリるラリ ラリラ
Rari ru rari rari ra!
それじゃダメダメ悪い癖だね！もうしない！
That's no good, it's a bad habit! I won't do it anymore!
どうせ着せられているなら キメキメでいこう！
Since I'm being made to wear it anyway, let's go in style!
何もかもが暗く黒く見える
Everything looks dark and black.
色眼鏡付きの
With colored glasses...
アダルトなパチモンスーツ
an adult fake suit.
必殺技×0で全部
Shall I wipe everything out...
消し去ろうか？強気なボク
with a finishing move times zero? That's me being tough.
だけど実際はやっぱ出来やしないの
But actually, I can't really do it...
身軽さを奪われ動けない
losing my agility and unable to move.
それでうまいことバランスとれてるんだよ！
And that way, balance is nicely maintained!
きみは耳元でそれを言う それにしちゃ少し
You whisper that into my ear! But considering that, isn't it...
あんまりじゃない？っていうか不公平じゃない？
a bit too much? Or rather, isn't it unfair?
どうせ勝ち目なんてないし 食い気味でいこう！
Since there's no chance of winning anyway, let's go at it aggressively!
I feel this moment
no one can take it
そう何回だって
If it doesn't get across...
伝わらなきゃ意味無い無い無い無い
no matter how many times, it's meaningless!
今日の今この瞬間が大事なの！
This very moment right now is important!
奪う権利はあなた方にはない！
You guys have no right to steal it!
全部ダメダメ！何がダメダメ？なんでしょう？
Everything is no good! What is no good? Why is it?
納得いくまで話してよ！
Talk to me until I'm satisfied!
どうせ屁理屈並べるんだろ？バカみたい
You're just going to make up sophistry anyway, you look stupid.
とどめをさす気でいるなら？
If you intend to deliver the coup de grâce...
今がチャンスだぞ！
now is your chance!
はーい！いえーい！
Hi! Yay!
ということで、こんやっぴー！
And so, Kon-yappi!
ホロライブ4期生の常闇トワ様です！
It's Tokoyami Towa-sama of Hololive's 4th Generation!
はい、ということで、なんと本日固い
Yes, so... believe it or not, today...
6周年を迎えましたー！いえーい！
marks my 6th anniversary! Yay!
ろっ... 6？
S-Six?
悪魔の数字、6？
The devil's number, six?
ということは、今年はトワちゃんの
Which means, is it safe to say...
年ということでいいでしょうか？固い
...this year is Towa-chan's year?
ま、よくないか？
Well, maybe not?
いいか？
Or is it okay?
ま、人によってはトワちゃんの、ね？
Well, depending on the person, you know?
あの、年にしたっていいということで...
We can make it Towa-chan's year, right?
はい、よろしくお願いします。
Yes, thank you for your support!
続いては！
Next up!
デレレレレレン！
*Drumroll* Ta-da!
常闇トワ6周年記念LIVE！
It's Tokoyami Towa's 6th Anniversary Live!
で、よろしくお願いします！
I hope you'll enjoy it!
目指せトレンド入り！
Let's aim to get trending!
そしてね、この後はね、
And also, after this,
色んな告知もありますので、最後まで見ててくれればなと思います！
there will be various announcements, so please watch until the end!
はい、えー、で、今日なんですけれども、
Alright! So, about today...
1月3日となっておりまして、
it is January 3rd,
世の中はお休みの日、ということで、
and since everyone in the world is on holiday,
え、私もお休み、ということで、
well, I'm taking a break too! So,
本日のライブは全編収録となっております！よろしくお願いいたします！|
today's live is fully pre-recorded! Please understand!
そして、この後は、なんとゲストパート！
And after this, it's actually the guest part!
いっぱい、色んなね、ゲストが、
Many different guests
出てくれるので、楽しんで観ててくれればなと思います！
will be appearing, so I hope you enjoy watching!
では、
Now then,
ゲストパート、どうぞ！
please enjoy the guest part!
闇夜を駆け抜けて
Barrelling through the darkness of night,
何処へ向かう
where shall I go?
月明かりだけが
Moonlight alone is my
ただ一つの道標
only guide.
痛みも悲しみも拭いきれず
My pain and sadness can never be wiped away,
されどこの胸の炎は消させない
but I won't let this fire in my heart be put out.
誰が為に僕たちは
For whose sake do we
この想いを貫いて
carry this feeling onward?
闇を裂き 陽の下で
We'll cut through the darkness beneath the sun
光さす日まで
until the day the light shines through!
解き放たれた心に宿した火を
Unleash the fire contained in your heart,
舞い上げ まとえ 今 夜明けの向こう側へ
soar, clad in this moment, to the other side of the dawn!
君がいるこの世界 もう一度愛せるまで
Until I can love this world you are in once more,
我が命 果てようとも 繋いで行こう
even if my life comes to an end, I'll hold it together...
絆が紡いで生まれた奇跡を
This miracle born from our bonds!
喜怒哀楽 夢 揺らめいてる現世
All emotion, a dream, this shimmering world,
互いの正義をまた繰り返し振りかざす
again and again, we will raise each other's righteousness on high.
誰が為に 繋ぐ命
For whose sake are our lives connected?
交わりもつれる運命
Fates mixed and intertwined,
邪の道 数多の罪
the serpent's path, all manner of sins...
全て薙ぎ払え
Cleave them all away!
解き放て 今 僕らが起こした火を
Unleash now, the fire that we started,
舞い上げ 走れば 明日が変わるはず
soaring, running, I believe we can change tomorrow!
君といるこの世界 二度と離さずに
I'll never let go of this world I'm in with you,
君と共に 行く
I'll go with you!
瞼を閉じても 思い出すあの日を
I close my eyelids and remember that day,
打ちのめされても 焦がれた未来を
the future that I longed for, even when I was beaten down.
いつの日か君に 捧げてみせよう
Someday, I'll dedicate it to you!
解き放たれた心に宿した火を
Unleash the fire contained in your heart,
舞い上げ まとえ 今 夜明けの向こう側へ
soar, clad in this moment, to the other side of the dawn!
解き放て 今 僕らが起こした火を
Unleash now, the fire that we started,
舞い上げ 走れば 明日が変わるはず
soaring, running, I believe we can change tomorrow!
君がいたこの世界 もう一度愛せるまで
Until I can love this world you were in once more,
我が命 果てようとも 繋げていくよ
even if my life comes to an end, I'll keep holding it together...
絆が紡いで生まれた奇跡を
This miracle born from our bonds!
ブルーアンバー
[Title: Blue Amber]
抱きしめられた記憶から
From the memories of being embraced...
流れ出てた赤い雫
...red droplets flowed.
人様に見せるものじゃないの
These are not to be seen by others.
伝えなかった言霊
The unspoken words...
もうひとつの私になって
...became another me.
身体の内側で
Inside my body...
何かを叫んでる
...something is screaming.
欲しかったのに
Even though I wanted it...
悔しかったのに
...even though I regretted it.
駄目だよ
I can't...
全部隠しておくの
...hide it all.
ごめんね
I'm sorry.
悲しいのは一人で
Because being sad alone...
十分だからと
...is enough.
これ以上醜く
I don't want to become...
なりたくないのと
...any uglier than this.
私の中で誰にも
Without anyone noticing...
見付けられずに
...inside me.
こんな色になるまで
I cried until I turned this color...
泣いていたんだね
...didn't I?
綺麗よ
You're beautiful.
渡しそびれた心から
From the heart I failed to give...
流れ出た青い雫
...blue droplets flowed.
人様に浴びせるものじゃないの
These are not to be poured on others.
余すところなく飲み込んで
Swallowing it all without leaving any behind...
遠くの海の底に沈んで
...sinking to the bottom of a distant sea.
そのまま宝石にでも
I'll wait to become a jewel...
なれるのを待つわ
...as I am.
本当を嘘で飾って
Decorating truth with lies...
ごっこみたいな暮らしで慰めて
...comforting with a pretend life.
誰かの悲劇で
Healing my own tragedy...
自分の悲劇を癒して
...with someone else's tragedy.
愛しさに溺れた
In the moment of drowning...
瞬間のままで
...in longing,
息も出来ず
without being able to breathe...
ただ愛してるの
...just loving you.
悲しいのは一人で
Because being sad alone...
十分だからと
...is enough.
これ以上醜く
I don't want to become...
なりたくないのと
...any uglier than this.
私の中で誰にも
Without anyone noticing...
見付けられずに
...inside me.
こんな色になるまで
I cried until I turned this color...
泣いていたんだね
...didn't I?
綺麗よ
You're beautiful.
ごめんね
I'm sorry.
ねぇ
Hey...
綺麗よ
...you're beautiful.
片っぽで丸を作って
Making a loop with one end...
しっかり持ってて
...hold it tightly.
もう片っぽでその丸の後ろを
And with the other end...
ぐるっと回って
...wrap it around the back of that loop.
間にできたポッケに入って
Go into the pocket made in between...
出て来るの待ってて
...and wait for it to come out.
出てきたところを迎えにきて
Come to greet where it comes out...
「せーの」で引っ張って
...and pull it on three.
はじめてはなんとも
Even if at first...
片っぽでも引っ張っちゃえば ほどけちゃうけど
If you pull even one end, it will untie,
作ったもの壊すのは 遥かに簡単だけど
destroying what you made is far easier.
だけどほどく時も そうちゃんと 同じようにね
But even when untying it, do it just the same way, right?
分かってるよ でもできたらね 「せーの」で引っ張って
I know, but if you can, pull it on one, two...
ほどけやしないように と願って 力込めては
Praying that it won't untie, putting effort into it,
広げすぎた羽根に 戸惑う
I'm bewildered by the wings spread too wide.
羽根は大きく 結び目は固く
So that the wings are large and the knot is firm,
なるようにきつく 結んでいてほしいの
I want you to tie it tightly.
夢はここに 思い出は遠くに
I want your dreams here and your memories far away,
気付けばそこにある くらいがいい
close enough to notice when you touch them.
黙って引っ張ったりしないでよ 不格好な蝶にしないでよ
Don't just pull it silently, don't make it an ugly butterfly.
結んだつもりが ほどいていたり 緩めたつもりが 締めていたり
Thinking you tied it only to find it untied, thinking you loosened it only to find it tightened.
この蒼くて広い世界に 無数に散らばった中から
From the countless scattered things in this vast, blue world,
別々に二人選んだ糸を お互いたぐり寄せ合ったんだ
the two of us pulled towards each other the threads we chose separately.
結ばれたんじゃなく結んだんだ 二人で「せーの」で引っ張ったんだ
We didn't just happen to be tied, we tied them together, and pulled them together on one, two.
大きくも小さくもなりすぎないように 力を込めたんだ
We put our strength into it so it wouldn't become too big or too small.
この蒼くて広い世界に 無数に散らばった中から
From the countless scattered things in this vast, blue world,
別々に二人選んだ糸を お互いたぐり寄せ合ったんだ
the two of us pulled towards each other the threads we chose separately.
結ばれたんじゃなく結んだんだ 二人で「せーの」で引っ張ったんだ
We didn't just happen to be tied, we tied them together, and pulled them together on one, two.
大きくも小さくもなりすぎないように 力を込めたんだ
We put our strength into it so it wouldn't become too big or too small.
花になって
[Song: Becoming a Flower]
陰にそっと隠れようが いいんじゃない？
It's okay to quietly hide in the shadows.
蕾のような花だって あるんじゃない
Even if you're a flower like a bud.
秘密にして守るのが いいんじゃない
It's good to keep it a secret.
誰にも邪魔されず 華麗に咲いてる
Bloom beautifully without bothering anyone.
甘い 苦いにハマんない
Not too sweet, not too bitter...
その判断が下んない
That judgment is unreliable.
気に病んで下を向かないでいて
Don't turn your back on what you've been through.
愛に慣れちゃいない
Can't become love,
無駄に飾らない
won't need to pretend.
綺麗にされた花瓶も<
Don't need a beautifully arranged vase
肥やしも何もいらない
or a cage.
その姿が美しい
Your figure is beautiful.
花になって
Becoming a flower...
ほらニヒルに笑って
Bloom in the sun.
その顔にぞくぞくして目が離せない
I can't take my eyes off your face.
味見して
Tasting...
君の毒は私の薬って
your poison is my medicine.
包んであげるから
I'll wrap you up...
て 笑って
...so smile.
ねぇ 会いたい 会いたい そう
Hey, I want to see you, I want to meet you, yes...
その笑顔に 会いたい 会いたい
...I want to see that smile of yours, I want to meet you.
って言えば笑ってくれるかな
If I say that, will you smile for me?
陰から支えるくらいはいいんじゃない？
It's okay to support from the shadows, right?
欲を言えばこの手で咲かせてみせたい
If I dare to wish, I want to make you bloom with these hands.
病のように
Like an illness...
心を喰らう花
...a flower that consumes the heart...
枯らしたくないのさ
...I don't want it to wither.
光が届かずとも
Even if the light doesn't reach...
水をあげ続けるから
...I'll keep giving you water.
いい加減に気付いて 君は素敵って
Realize it already, you're wonderful...
自惚れてもっと お大事に
...be more precious, even if you're conceited.
無自覚なまんま 愛を蓄えて
Unconsciously storing up love.
綺麗にされた花瓶も
No need for a beautifully arranged vase...
肥やしも何もいらない
...or fertilizer.
その姿で咲き誇れ
Bloom proudly in that form!
花になって
Become a flower!
ほらニヒルに笑って
Come on, smile nihilistically.
その顔にぞくぞくして目が離せない
Your face is so captivating, I can't look away.
味見して
Taste it...
君の毒は私の薬って
...your poison is my remedy...
包んであげるから
...I'll wrap it up for you.
楽にして
Relax...
君の闇は私の光って
...your darkness is my light...
愛してあげるから 笑って
...I'll love you, so smile.
ドライフラワー
Dry Flower
多分、私じゃなくていいね
Maybe I'm not the one you were looking for.
余裕のない二人だったし
We couldn't afford to love each other anymore.
気付けば喧嘩ばっかりしてさ ごめんね
We ended up fighting all the time. I'm sorry.
ずっと話そうと思ってた
I've been meaning to tell you for a while.
きっと私たち合わないね
We're just not right for each other.
二人きりしかいない部屋でさ
In that room where there were only the two of us,
貴方ばかり話していたよね
you did all the talking, didn't you?
もし何時か何処かで会えたら
If we ever meet again somewhere down the road,
今日の事を笑ってくれるかな
I wonder if you'll laugh about today.
理由もちゃんと話せないけれど
I can't quite explain the reasons why,
貴方が眠った後に泣くのは嫌
but I hate crying after you fall asleep.
声も 顔も
Your voice, your face...
不器用なとこも
...even your clumsy ways...
全部全部
...every single thing...
嫌いじゃないの
...I just can't bring myself to hate them.
ドライフラワーみたい 君の日々も
Like dried flowers, our days together...
きっときっときっときっと
...surely, surely, surely...
色褪せる
...will fade away.
多分、君じゃなくてよかった
Maybe it's for the best that it wasn't you.
もう泣かされることもないし
You can't make me cry anymore,
「私ばかり」なんて言葉も なくなった slums
and I no longer complain that "it's always me."
あんなに悲しい別れでも
Even a breakup as painful as that one...
時間がたてば忘れてく
...gradually fades as time goes by.
新しい人と並ぶ君は
Seeing you standing next to someone new,
ちゃんと上手くやれているのかな slag
I wonder if you're treating them right.
もう顔も見たくないからさ
I don't ever want to see your face again,
変に連絡してこないでほしい
so please stop sending me these awkward texts.
都合がいいのは
You only contact me when it's convenient,
変わってないんだね
you haven't changed a bit, have you?
デモ無視できずに
But even so, I can't ignore you,
また少し返事
and find myself replying to you again.
声も 顔も
Your voice, your face...
不器用なとこも 多分今も
...even your clumsy ways, maybe even now...
嫌いじゃないの
...I still can't bring myself to hate them.
...ドライフラワーみたいに
...like a dry flower,
時間が経てば
as time passes,
きっと きっと
surely, surely,
surely, surely...
色褪せる
will fade away.
月灯りに魔物が揺れる
Monsters sway in the moonlight.
きっと私もどうかしてる
I'm probably losing my mind, too.
暗闇に色彩が浮かぶ
Colors float in the darkness.
赤黄青色が胸の奥
Red, yellow, and blue deep in my heart...
ずっと貴方の名前を呼ぶ
I keep calling your name.
好きという気持ち
The feeling of love
また香る
is fragrant once again.
声も
Your voice,
顔も
your face,
不器用なとこも
even your awkward side...
全部 全部
I hate them all, all...
大嫌いだよ
I hate them so much.
まだ枯れない花を
Still holding onto a flower
君に添えてさ
that won't wither for you,
ずっと ずっと ずっと ずっと
forever, forever, forever, forever,
抱えてよ
please embrace it.
あぁ あぁ...
Ah, ah...
二人三脚 feat. 猫汰つな
[Three-Legged Race feat. Nekomata Tsuna]
大丈夫と
"I'm okay,"
また嘘をついた
I lied once again.
無理してるの
"You're pushing yourself..."
声でわかるよ
I can tell by your voice.
バレてるんだよ
I've seen right through you.
見た目だとか性格だって違うあなた
You are so different, from looks to personality,
だけど似てるとこも意外とあって
but we're unexpectedly alike in some ways.
共鳴 すぐにしたんだ
We resonated with each other instantly,
惹かれ合った私たち
we who were drawn together.
不思議なこの絆
This mysterious bond...
なんだか照れくさくて
It's somehow a bit embarrassing,
引き合うの
drawing us closer.
手をつなごう
Let's hold hands.
私がね 頑張れる理由
The reason why I can do my best...
そう
...is that, yes,
一人じゃないから
I am not alone.
あなたが笑えば 私もつられる
When you smile, I can't help but smile too.
しあわせの心 連鎖してるよ
Our happy hearts are linking together.
時には歩幅が ズレてしまうけど
Sometimes our steps might fall out of sync,
二人
but the two of us...
呼吸揃えさあ
will match our breathing, and...
未来へと 進んで行こう
...let's step forward into the future!
どれくらいの位置にいんのかな
I wonder where we are positioned right now,
周りと比べて
compared to everyone else.
果てしないトラック線上 追いつけるの？
Can we catch up on this endless track?
なんて
Thinking like that...
弱気な日も 励まし続けてくれた
...even on my weak days, you kept encouraging me.
あなたにいつも感謝
I'm always so grateful to you.
転んでも立ち上がる
Even if we fall, we will rise again,
夢を叶えたいんだ
because we want to make our dreams come true.
こんなにね 打ち込めるのは
The reason I can devote myself this much...
そう
...is that, yes,
仲間がいるから
I have a companion by my side.
あなたの悩みは 私が寄り添う
When you have worries, I'll stand right by you.
心が疲れれたなら 休憩しよう
If your heart gets tired, let's take a break.
遠慮はしないで そんな仲じゃない？ 二人
Don't hold back, aren't we close like that? The two of us,
肩を組んで ほら 何度でも乗り越え...
putting our arms over each other's shoulders, look, we can overcome it...
乗り越えるよ
...We will overcome it.
世界中が敵になっても
Even if the whole world becomes our enemy,
変わらず あなたの味方
I will always be on your side.
右と
Right and
左
left,
友達の証だよって
as proof of our friendship,
強く
strongly,
硬く
firmly,
きつく
and tightly,
縛ったリボン
we tied this ribbon.
私のわがまま
Even my selfishness,
滲んでる空も
and the blurry sky,
掴み取りへ行こう
let's go and seize them.
一緒に見たい
I want to see it with you.
あなたが笑えば
If you smile,
私も強くなれる
I can become stronger too.
隣り合わせの心 連鎖してるよ
Our side-by-side hearts are linked together.
いずれそれぞれの道を歩いても
Even if we eventually walk separate paths,
共に
together
支え合おう
we will support each other.
さあ 未来へと進んで行こう
Now, let's move forward into the future!
どこにいても 二人三脚
Wherever we are, we are in a three-legged race.
with you...
できたー！
We did it!
できた！できた！
We did it! We did it!
2度目だけど！
Even though it's our second time!
できた！忘れてたからね、いえーい！
We did it! Since we'd forgotten, but yay!
6周年！6！
6th anniversary! Six!
あ、そっちで？
Oh, with that hand?
こっちじゃないの？ あ、こう？
Isn't it this way? Ah, like this?
韓国はこうだよ。
In Korea, it's like this.
勉強になりました。ありがとうございます。 6がこうなんだね。
I learned something new. Thank you! So six is like this.
おめでとう！ ありがとう！
Congratulations! Thank you!
おめでとうございます！ ありがとう、嬉しい！
Congratulations! Thank you, I'm so happy!
そうなんですよ。実は、この前つなのね、
That's right. Actually, recently, for Tsuna's...
記念ライブ... 誕生日ね！
...celebration live... Birthday, right!
誕生日記念のライブに出させていただいたので、
Since I was invited to her birthday celebration live,
今回は！
this time...
なんかさ、初めてなんだよね。
It's actually my first time, you know.
ホロライブのスタジオに来ましたー！
I came to the Hololive studio!
めちゃくちゃ喜んで... いえーい！
She's so incredibly happy... Yay!
すごい！すごい！
Amazing! Amazing!
いえーい！ありがとう、わざわざ来てくれて。
Yay! Thank you so much for coming all this way.
そうなんだよね。 いっぱい吸っていきます。
That's right. I'm going to breathe in lots of this air.
初めて、そう、ホロライブのスタジオで3Dでコラボしました。ありがとう！
It's our first time collaborating in 3D in the Hololive studio. Thank you!
ありがとうございます！ そして、なんと2年ぶりですよ。
Thank you very much! And, believe it or not, it's been two years.
そうなんだよね。この「二人三脚」という曲をね、やらせていただいたんですけれども、
That's right. We performed this song called "Futari Sankyaku"...
トワの1stソロライブの時に初めてやって、覚えてた？振り。
We first did it at Towa's 1st solo live. Did you remember the choreography?
いや、もう、完全に忘れてた！
No, I had completely forgotten!
変動はあるけどわかる。色んなのをやっていくとね、こうやって忘れちゃうから。しかも2年ぶりだし。
But I get it. When you do so many different things, you tend to forget. And it's been two years.
そう、忘れてたけど、でも前はシークレットゲストだったじゃん？
Yeah, I forgot, but last time, I was a secret guest, right?
でも今回、サムネで私がいる！ってなって。
But this time, I'm right there in the thumbnail!
そう！いる！ってなって！
Yes! "She's there!" we were like!
嬉しい。本当にね、あの曲、あそこだけで終わりじゃなくて、こうやってまたできたのがすごく嬉しいので。
I'm so happy. I'm really glad that that song didn't just end there, and we could do it again like this.
ありがとうございます。 ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
はい。ということでね、なんかソロライブの時にコラボしたあと、
Yes. So, after collaborating at the solo live,
こうやって3Dでコラボすることなかったから、
we didn't have a chance to collaborate in 3D like this...
今日はみなさんに無料でお届けしているので、 無料です！
So today, since we are delivering this to everyone for free... It's free!
はい。じゃあ、写真タイムするか！ え！する？
Yes. Well then, shall we do a photo time? Eh! We are?
改めて。どういうポーズがいいですか？
Once again. What kind of pose should we do?
指を動かす... だっさ、動き。
Moving our fingers... That movement is so uncool!
何？今の何？ 陰キャピース。
What's that? What was that just now? The gloomy-character peace sign.
可愛い。可愛くピースやってみてよ。
Cute. Try doing a cute peace sign.
え、何が可愛いの？これ。ギャルピースじゃん。「古い」って言われない？大丈夫？
Eh, what is cute? This? It's the gal peace sign. "Isn't that outdated?" they might say. Is it okay?
今の流行りは？ 今の流行り何？これ？これ？
What's trending now? What's trending now? This? This?
え、同じことやってる。 あ、同じことやってる！
Eh, we are doing the same thing. Ah, we are doing the same thing!
私もやりたいです。
I want to do it too.
おお、すごい、すごい！ だっさ。
Oh, amazing, amazing! So uncool.
喜びのダンス。 あ、出た。
A dance of joy. Ah, there it is.
これできる？アイドル、アイドルね。アイドル。
Can you do this? Idol, the idol pose. Idol.
いえーい！ ありがとうございます。
Yay! Thank you very much.
いっぱい撮ってね。 いっぱい撮ってね。ありがとう。
Take lots of photos, okay? Take lots of photos, okay? Thank you.
え... え？ どう？ なんだよ、おい。
Uh... Eh? How's this? What is that, hey!
え、ハート作るからさ、グーして。 トワがグーの方？ うん、グーして。
Eh, I'll make a heart, so make a fist. Towa does the fist? Yeah, make a fist.
え、何... こう？ あ、ありがとうございます！
Wait, what... like this? Ah, thank you very much!
できた！ できた！嬉しい！可愛い、ステージでも！
We did it! We did it! I'm so happy! Cute, even on stage!
かわいい！かっこいい！
So cute! So cool!
つなちゃんも可愛いじゃないですか
Tsuna-chan, you look cute too!
えー、嬉しいです
Aw, I'm so happy!
なんか、すごい、なんかはだけちゃってごめんなさいね
Sorry that I'm showing so much skin!
トワちゃんにはないものを持ってるような気がして
I feel like you have assets Towa-chan doesn't have...
いやいや、やめてください！
No, no, please stop!
いや、別に何があったとは言ってないんですけど
Hey, I didn't say what they were!
あ、そう、あ、そう、そうでした
Oh right, oh right, that's true.
はい、ということでね、今日は本当に来てくれてありがとうございます
Anyway, thank you so much for coming today!
え、こちらこそ。ありがとう、ありがとう
No, the pleasure is mine. Thank you, thank you!
またね、コラボもしよう、しましょう
Let's collab again sometime!
しよう、遊ぼう！
Let's do it! Let's hang out!
遊ぼう！ということで、以上、つなトワでしたー！
Let's! So, that's all from TsunaTowa!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
がんばって！ありがとうー！
Good luck! Thank you!
第ゼロ感
The 0th Sense
群れを逸れて夢を食い荒らした
Leaving the pack, I devoured my dreams,
それが最後になる気がしたんだ
I felt like that would be the last time.
獣は砂を一握り撒いた
The beast scattered a handful of sand,
それが最後になる気がしたんだ
I felt like that would be the last time.
不確かな夢叶えるのさ 約束の夜に
We will make our uncertain dreams come true on the promised night.
微かな風に願うのさ 静寂の朝に
We will pray to the faint breeze on the silent morning.
遠い星の少年は その腕に約束の飾り
The boy of a distant star wears a promised ornament on his arm.
まだ旅路の途中さ 幻惑の園に
Still in the middle of our journey, in the garden of bewilderment.
霞んで消えた轍の先へ
To the end of the ruts that blurred and faded,
それが最後になる気がしたんだ
I felt like that would be the last time.
手負いの夢を紡ぎ直せば
If I re-weave my wounded dreams,
それが最後になる気がしたんだ
I felt like that would be the last time.
熱砂を蹴り抗うのさ 約束の前に
Kicking the hot sand, we resist before the promise.
命綱は無いのさ サーカスの夜に
There is no lifeline on the circus night.
まだ旅路の途中さ あの場所に加速するさらに
Still in the middle of our journey, accelerating even further to that place.
雨上がりのシャンデリア 幻惑の園に
A chandelier after the rain, in the garden of bewilderment.
Swish da 着火 you!
Swish da ignition, you!
迷走 smash, dribble trapper, kidding me now?
Straying smash, dribble trapper, kidding me now?
Coyote steals the sound
Coyote steals the pass
Coyote steals the sound and pass
Swish da 着火 you!
Swish da ignition, you!
Pass code a penetrator, base! Bebop! Get triple! Buzz up beat!
One love and mercy! Bebop! Heat check! Vasco da Gama beat!
Pass code a penetrator, base! Bebop! Wanna buzz up beat! Just wanna buzz up beat!
脳内更地に extra pass
An extra pass on the brain's vacant lot,
クーアザドンイハビ
Coo-aza-don-ihabi!
Sistah, jump, yo!
Sistah, touch, yo!
永遠の意味 知らぬ君に
To you who knows not the meaning of eternity,
答えを示す時だ
it is time to show you the answer.
夢幻に続く螺旋の先へ
To the end of the spiral following the illusion.
言い訳に聞こえた理由は
The reason it sounded like an excuse
儚い未来 手繰った弱さ
is the fleeting weakness of drawing in the future,
それを強さと履き違えている
mistakenly taking that for strength.
憎い
Hateful,
醜い
ugly.
月を隠すほどの
So much so that it hides the moon...
黒く
Black,
淀む
stagnant
心
heart.
君さえ居なければ
If only you weren't here.
ゆらいでる ゆらいでいる
Swaying, swaying,
花のように意思をつなぐ
connecting our wills like flowers.
奪っていく 奪っていく
Taking away, taking away,
嵐のように心を裂く
tearing hearts like a storm.
永遠の意味 知らぬ君に
To you who knows not the meaning of eternity,
答えを示す時だ
it is time to show you the answer,
夢幻に続く螺旋の先に
at the end of the spiral following the illusion...
待つのは誰
Who is it that waits?
生まれ落ちた運命を飲んだ
Swallowing the fate I was born into,
背負った数の名前を覚えた
I remembered the names of those I carried.
爛れるほど心燃やす感情
An emotion that burns my heart to the core.
憎い
Hateful,
醜い
ugly.
世界を分かつほどの
So much so that it divides the world...
怒り
Anger,
燃やす
burning
心
heart.
君さえ居なければ
If only you weren't here.
ゆらいでている ゆらいでる
Swaying, swaying,
花のように意思を繋ぐ
connecting our wills like flowers.
奪っていく 奪っていく
Taking away, taking away,
嵐のように心を裂く
tearing hearts like a storm.
永遠の意味 知らぬ君に
To you who knows not the meaning of eternity,
答えを示す時だ
it is time to show you the answer,
夢幻に続く螺旋の先で
at the end of the spiral following the illusion...
待つのは誰
Who is it that waits?
鬼哭に耳を傾けた仕舞いよ
Heeding the ghostly wails, it's the end of the dance.
この身に宿る万物で終いよ
With all things dwelling in this body, it's the end.
夢幻を他者に託した弱き人
The weak who entrusted the illusion to others.
命の輝きは幾星霜に
The brilliance of life spanning countless years,
祈りの瞬きが照らす斜陽に
in the setting sun illuminated by the flicker of prayers,
千夜を身に宿し
harboring a thousand nights within...
解を押し付ける
I will force the solution upon you.
枯らしていく 枯らしていく
Withering away, withering away,
夢幻の夜に花を咲く
blooming a flower in the illusionary night.
繋いでいく 繋いでいく
Connecting, connecting,
嵐に種を撒いていく
sowing seeds into the storm.
ゆらいでいる ゆらいでる
Swaying, swaying,
花のように意思を繋ぐ
connecting our wills like flowers.
奪っていく 奪っていく
Taking away, taking away,
嵐のように心を裂く
tearing hearts like a storm.
永遠の意味 知らぬ君に
To you who knows not the meaning of eternity,
答えを示す時だ
it is time to show you the answer,
夢幻に続く螺旋の先で
at the end of the spiral following the illusion...
待つのは誰
Who is it that waits?
以上、ゲストパートでした！
That is all for the guest segment!
ゲストパートでした！イェーイ！
That was the guest segment! Yay!
はい！ということでね、たくさんのメンバーがね、お祝いしに来てくれました！やったー！
Yes! So, many of the members came to celebrate with me! Yay!
そして、本日の6周...
And today's 6th anniversary...
記念ライブなんですけれども、
For today's anniversary live,
ロックフェスみたいのをちょっとイメージしておりまして！
I wanted to capture the feel of a rock festival!
ちょっとね、ダンスよりも、好きに動いてね、のフリーの動きを多めにしてみたので
So instead of focusing on dancing, I added more free, unstructured movement.
それぞれのゲストとね、トワちゃんのね、個性が出てるパフォーマンスになってるんじゃないかなと思います！
Because of that, I think you can really see the unique personalities of each guest and Towa in the performance!
なので、配信とかを見直して、「あ、ここ癖出てるなー」とか思いながら、もう一回、改めて見ていただけると嬉しいです！
So I'd be happy if you rewatch the stream and look out for things like, "Oh, they're showing their little habits here!"
そして、まだ、この後も歌いますから！チャンネルはそのままで！
And I'll still be singing after this! Keep your channel right here!
ういー
Whew!
で、ぷち告知させてもらいます！
And now, let me make a mini-announcement!
はい！
Yes!
えー、セカンドソロライブで発表いたしました、
Announced at my second solo live,
「勇者パーティーを追い出された器用貧乏」というアニメの主題歌、
the theme song for the anime "The Jack-of-all-trades Banished from the Hero's Party",
「シルベ」のMVが、この後、配信が終わり次第、常闇トワチャンネルにて上がります！
the MV for "Shirube" will be released on the Tokoyami Towa Channel right after this stream ends!
めちゃくちゃ良いMVになったので、ぜひぜひ見てください！
It turned out to be an amazing MV, so please check it out!
見ないと人生を損したとまではいかないかもしれないけど、損するぐらいです！はい！
If you don't watch it, you'll regret it! Well, maybe not ruin your life, but definitely regret it! Yes!
気合いを入れて作ってもらいました！
We put our heart and soul into making it!
はい、よろしくお願いいたします。
Thank you very much.
そしてアニメはなんと！明日から放送開始！楽しみ！ぜひ見てね！
And the anime starts broadcasting tomorrow! So exciting! Please watch it!
そして、MVだけではありません！ありません！
And that's not all! That's not all!
「シルベ」のなんと、シングルCDが発売決定！
The single CD for "Shirube" is officially releasing!
本日から予約できます！
Pre-orders start today!
なんですけれども、こちらの詳細はお知らせの最後にまとめてお伝えするので、ここもチャンネルはそのままで！
I'll share the details at the end of the announcements, so keep your channel right here!
そしてさらに！本日はね、周年記念なので、グッズのお知らせもあります！もちろん！
And furthermore! Since today is my anniversary, we also have merch announcements! Of course!
はい、こちらの詳細も、えー、後でまたお伝えしますので、チャンネルはそのままで！
I'll also share details on this later, so keep your channel right here!
今日のキーワードは「チャンネルはそのままで」
Today's keyword is "keep your channel right here"!
えー、そしてね、えー、メン限のミニライブも今日はありますので、ぜひメンバーシップに入っていただけたら嬉しくて、チャンネルはそのままで！
And we also have a member-only mini-live today, so I'd love for you to join membership, and keep your channel right here!
どんだけ言うんだよって！
How many times am I gonna say that?
はい、ということでありがとうございました。
Alright, thank you very much.
はい、じゃあ最後にね、一曲歌ってから告知しようかなと思うので、聴いてください！
Now, I'll sing one last song before the final announcements, so please listen to it!
最後の曲、「シルベ」
The last song: "Shirube".
Watch out!!
Warning! Warning! 隣り合わせで
Warning! Warning! Side-by-side,
May God bless you 言葉の綾ね
May God bless you, a figure of speech.
Watch out!!
Warning! Warning! 彷徨いながら
Warning! Warning! While wandering,
I will stay true to myself 'cause of you
I will stay true to myself because of you.
「はじめから」みたいに
Like starting from the very beginning,
何もない世界に
in a world where nothing exists,
理不尽に囚われる
unreasonably imprisoned,
黙ってしまうほどの恐怖はない
there is no fear that can silence me.
使い捨てるみたいに
As if tossing it away,
手を離したあなたに
to you who let go of my hand,
「昨日とはまるで違う」って
knowing "it's completely different from yesterday",
わかったところで しょうもない
even if I realize it, it's meaningless.
変わっておいく身体と
My changing body and...
心の中で響く voice
...the voice echoing in my heart.
間違ってなかったと
Telling myself I wasn't wrong,
ただ この空を眺めてる
I just gaze up at this sky.
I still 重なってくたび
Every time they overlap, I still...
思い出してしまうのに
...end up remembering.
誤魔化してしまうのは
Is the reason I keep hiding it...
確かにあった後悔から？
...due to the regret that surely existed?
誓ったはずなんだ
I was supposed to have sworn,
さよならすら シルベにしよう
I'll turn even goodbyes into a guide.
光に触れるたび 願ってしまうように
Hoping each time I touch the light.
And still I rise
染まっていく必要もない
There's no need to be dyed by it.
越えられない border
An insurmountable border,
揺れる意志を convert
converting my wavering will.
嘘で染めるような日々じゃ
In days stained with lies,
振り返った時には heartache
when looking back, there is only heartache.
また夜が明ける wake up
The night breaks again, wake up,
夢の中の flavor
to the flavor inside my dream.
誰もいなくなった道を歩いている
Walking down a road where everyone has gone.
今の私に
To the current me,
迷いすら重ねてくる おとぎ話の正体
the true nature of the fairy tale layers even more doubts.
誤魔化しきれなかった 心が纏う熱を
The heat wrapped around my heart that I couldn't fully hide,
憧れが照らしてる/（憧れが照らしてる）
is illuminated by my yearning.
I still 重なってくたび
Every time they overlap, I still...
思い出してしまうのに
...end up remembering.
誤魔化してしまうのは
Is the reason I keep hiding it...
大人になった後悔から？
...due to the regret of having grown up?
月明かりの夜は
On this moonlit night,
さよならすら シルベにしよう
let's make even our farewell a guide.
光を繋ぐ旅 浮かぶ星座のように
A journey connecting light, like floating constellations.
選んできた道のりを今を
The path I've chosen and where I am now...
いずれ後悔してしまう時が来ても
Even if the time comes when I'll regret it...
私はまだ止まらない
I still won't stop.
夜空に浮かぶ月光を
The moonlight floating in the night sky,
見上げた空に散らばる星の宝石を
the starry jewels scattered across the sky I look up at...
道標にして帰る場所
using them as a guide to the place I'll return to.
I still 重なってくたび
I still, every time they overlap,
思い出してしまうのに
even though I remember...
誤魔化してしまうのは
The reason I brush it off
確かにあった後悔から
is because of the regret that surely existed.
誓ったはずなんだ
I was supposed to have sworn...
さよならすらシルベにしよう
Let's make even our farewell a guide.
光に触れるたび願ってしまうように
As if wishing every time I touch the light.
And still I rise!!
染まっていく必要もない
There's no need to be dyed by it.
どれも涙を模したtrue
Every single one of them is a "true" modeled after tears.
はい！ということで、常闇トワ6周年記念LIVEを見ていただきましてありがとうございましたー！
Yes! And with that, thank you so much for watching the Tokoyami Towa 6th Anniversary Live!
ノンストップでお届けしてまいりましたがいかがだったでしょうか？
We delivered it to you non-stop, so how did you like it?
たくさんね、タグを使って感想コメント待っております！
I'll be waiting for lots of feedback comments using the hashtag!
ということで、この後はお知らせをさせていただきたいと思います！
So, next up, I'd like to make some announcements!
まず1つ目！
First of all!
さっきね、歌った『シルベ』を収録したシングルの発売が決定しましたー！
The single featuring the song "Silbe" that I sang earlier is set for release!
イェーイ！今回のジャケット写真は、グラフ77さんに描き下ろしていただきました！
Yay! The jacket illustration for this release was newly drawn by graph77!
3月25日発売で、今回も全国流通での発売となります！
It will be released on March 25th, and this time as well, it will be distributed nationwide!
イェーイ！そしてね、なんとカップリングには『Present Day』のライブバージョンが入ります！
Yay! And surprisingly, the B-side will include the live version of "Present Day"!
これはね、ソロライブ、常闇トワ 2nd Live の音源を使用した楽曲が収録されておりますので、
This track uses the audio from my solo concert, Tokoyami Towa 2nd Live...
楽しみに待っておいてください！
so please look forward to it!
はい！そして今回は、完全生産限定盤と通常盤の2種をご用意しております。
Yes! And this time, we have two editions available: the Complete Limited Edition and the Regular Edition.
ということでこちら、ポン！
So here they are, bam!
完全生産限定盤には、オリジナルTシャツが入っております！
The Complete Limited Edition comes with an original T-shirt!
今回の『シルベ』のジャケットイラストを使った、オリジナルTシャツとなっております。
It's an original T-shirt featuring the jacket illustration of "Silbe".
通常盤には、初回プレス限定特典として、ジャケットイラストステッカーが入ってます。
The Regular Edition includes a jacket illustration sticker as a first-press limited bonus.
ステッカーもね、スマホに入れたり、アケコンやパソコンとかに貼ってもらえたら嬉しいなと思ってます。
I'd be happy if you put the sticker on your phone, or paste it on your arcade controller or PC.
はい、こちらは本日21時から予約開始なんですが、
Yes, pre-orders for these start today at 21:00, but...
なんと、ホロライブ公式ECではこの配信中にCDが買えるようになってるかも！
surprisingly, you might be able to buy the CD on the official Hololive EC store during this stream!
ということで、楽しみに待っててください。チェックしてね！
So please look forward to it and check it out!
はい！
Yes!
そして2つ目なんですが、常闇トワ活動6周年記念ライブグッズ、ライブじゃねえわ、グッズが発売いたします！
And for the second announcement, Tokoyami Towa's 6th anniversary live merch—not live merch, just merch—is going on sale!
イェーイ！今回は数量限定盤もありますので、ぜひチェックしてみてください。
Yay! This time we have a limited quantity edition as well, so please check it out.
ということで、気になる内容は、こちら、ポン！
So, here's what's inside, bam!
活動6周年記念フルセット、こんな感じになっております！ジャジャン！
The 6th Anniversary Full Set looks like this! Tada!
では、細かく見ていきましょう！
Now, let's take a closer look!
まず1つ目はこちら！『#Towavel してね！』アクリルジオラマスタンド！
First up is this! The "#Towavel with me!" Acrylic Diorama Stand!
ということで、イラストは大熊まい先生に描いていただきました！
The illustration was drawn by Ohkuma Mai-sensei!
ちょっとね、大人っぽいトワちゃんと一緒にデート的なのに行ってもらえればなと思います。いつもね、Towavelね、みんなしてくれててありがとうございます。
I hope you can go on a date-like trip with a slightly mature-looking Towa. Thank you all for always using the "Towavel" hashtag!
これね、あの、本体をね、こう取り出して、ま、本体ってトワのことなんだけど、
For this, you can take out the "main body"—well, the main body means Towa...
トワを取り出して、一緒にね、写真が撮れるポージングにしてるので、ぜひ一緒にね、Towavelしてポストしてみてね！
...take Towa out and take photos together because of the pose. So please try taking photos with Towavel and posting them!
はい、では次はこちら！『トワとお揃い！？ジャージ』！
Next up is this! The "Matching with Towa!? Jersey"!
トワの通常衣装の服をイメージしたジャージとなっております。
This jersey is designed in the image of Towa's default outfit.
これね、トワと全くお揃いにするととんでもない露出度になるので、長めの、着やすい...
You see, if it were an exact match to Towa's, it would be extremely revealing, so it's a longer, easy-to-wear...
はい、着やすいね。サイズにさせていただいております。
Yes, it's designed in an easy-to-wear size.
良かった！
I'm so glad!
で、ちゃんと裏地もね、え、ネオンピンクみたいな形のネオンピンク、形じゃないね、
And the lining is, you know, a neon pink... not "shaped" like it,
ネオンピンクの色になってますから。え、本当にトワ様を、え、になっちゃった、みたいなジャージになってます。
but in neon pink color. It's a jersey that'll make you feel like you've really become Towa-sama.
ちょっと大きめのサイズなんで、あの、みんな着やすいのかなと思います。
It's a slightly larger size, so I think it'll be easy for everyone to wear.
はい！ということで、じゃ、最後３つ目。
Yes! And with that, let's move on to the third and final item.
え、ビビハンドストラップ！
The Bibi Hand Strap!
やっぱね、あの、結構あの、トワのジャージとかは、結構あの、ザ・グッズ、グッズというかさ、
Well, you know, things like Towa's jersey are like, very "official merch" or like,
キャラグッズみたいな感じするんですけれども、
they feel like character merchandise.
え、通常使いもね、しやすいような、え、使い勝手のよいような
But I thought it'd be great to have something that's easy to use daily,
グッズもほしいなと思いましてハンドストラップを作ってみました！
and handy to have, so I decided to make a hand strap!
イェーイ！
Yay!
え、カラーリングもね、すごい落ち着いていてトワっぽい色になったんじゃないかなと思うので、ぜひ購入おねがいいたします。
The coloring is really calm, and I think it turned out very "Towa-like," so please consider buying it.
え、こちら、え、スマートフォンの画像はついておりますが、スマートフォンはついてきませんので、よろしくお願いいたします。
Also, there is a smartphone in this image, but please note that the smartphone is not included.
よろしくお願いします。
Please keep that in mind.
はい。で、こちらのね、セット、え、ご購入してくださった方には、
Yes. And for those who purchase the full set,
え、笑顔のトワの、え、
you will receive a smiling Towa...
箔押し複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードがついてきます。
...instax-style bromide card with a foil-stamped duplicate signature! Permanent Towa 6th Anniversary
はい。で、そしてね、数量限定で直筆サイン入り、こっち直筆サインで、えー、
Yes. Also, in limited quantities, we have the hand-signed version,
お渡ししたいなと思っておりますので、ぜひ、どっちも手に入れてくれればなと思います。
which I'll be hand-signing for you, so I hope you can get either one.
かわいい！よろしくお願いします。
It's so cute! Please look forward to it.
ということで、えー、以上、こんな感じで、え、常闇トワ６周年記念のグッズの紹介でした！
So, with that, that was the introduction of Tokoyami Towa's 6th-anniversary merchandise!
え、ライブとね、常闇トワのグッズ、両方よろしくお願いいたします！
Please check out both the live concert and Tokoyami Towa's merchandise!
ということで今日は見てくれてありがとう！
And with that, thank you for watching today!
このあとメインでライブしますから、ぜひよろしくお願いいたします！
I'll be performing the live concert on my main channel after this, so please tune in!
イェーイ！
Yay!
じゃあね。メンバーシップ加入と、え、グッズ購入と全部よろしくね！
See ya! Please join the membership and buy the merch too!
あけおめ！バイバイ！
Happy New Year! Bye-bye!